HAYK PETROSYAN

Risk Manager, Gymnastics Coach

Gymnastic coach who is responsible, approachable and able to understand the other person's perspectives with positive motivating skills and dedicated and focused on what he wants. Been engaged in professional gymnastics for 17 years. Been a member of the Armenian national youth gymnastics team. In 2011, set a new world record by performing the 386 giants on High Bar. Two-time champion of the youth of Armenia. Participated with the national team in 2013 at the European Youth Olympic Festival in the Netherlands, as well as at the World Gymnasiade in Brazil, taking 13th place on Rings. Since 2015 have worked as a gymnastics coach. Besides this, working as Risk Manager.



EXPERIENCE

Antarayin 160/9, Yerevan November 2020 - Present

Risk Manager

Play Master

- · Responsible for team's work
- · Found rising problems and gave solutions to those
- Followed company's well-being and that the works will be well done
- Handled customer complaints with empathy and composure.
- · Consistently met my short and long-term targets.
- Proactively participated in meetings and helped create new practices.

Moskovyan 3, Yerevan September 2015 - Present

Gymnastic Coach

Artistic Gymnastics Olympic school after Albert Azaryan

- Teaching gymnastics both individually and with a group
- Developing the kids/children strength and flexibility, teaching new gymnastics elements
- Elevate kids/children levels
- Theory of gymnastics. Practicing gymnastic skills
- · Visualizing and teaching
- · Sports psychology
- Preparation for competitions. Improving the class of gymnast
- Artistic of Gymnastics Code of Points. Judging
- Designed classes to match the learning levels and skills of all participants
- Tracked class attendance and monitored size to gauge the effectiveness of promotions
- Collaborated with club owners to develop new gymanastic classes

Moskovyan 3, Yerevan March 2012 - January 2018

National Team Member

Gymnastics Federation of Armenia

- International Record Holder, 2011 386 giants on High Bar
- International tournament after Hrant Shahinyan, 2010 All Around 3rd place
- International tournament after Hrant Shahinyan, 2011 All Around 3rd place
- Armenian Youth Championships, 2012 Rings 1st place
- Armenian Youth Championships, 2013 All Around 2nd place

CONTACT INFORMATION

Email

haykgym@gmail.com

Address

Nor Nork 8th Massive 35/10, Yerevan

Phone

+37477597927

Date of birth

07-10-1996

Nationality

Armenian

Link

https://www.linkedin.com/i n/hayk-petrosyan-32121321 1/

SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Problem-Solving
- Customer service
- Sales
- Leadership
- Theory of Gymnastics:
 Practicing Gymnastic
 skills, techniques of
 Gymnastic skills, teaching:
 Differential treatment to
 each athlete: Sports
 Psychology: Motivational
 Speech

LANGUAGES

English

Intermediate

Russian

Intermediate

Georgian

Intermediate

Armenian

Advanced

- Armenian Youth Championships, 2013 Rings 1st place
- Armenian Youth Championships, 2013 Vault 3rd place
- Armenian Youth Championships, 2013 FX 3rd place
- International tournament after Hrant Shahinyan, 2013 All Around 2nd place
- International tournament after Hrant Shahinyan, 2013 High Bar 2nd place
- International tournament after Hrant Shahinyan, 2013 Vault 3rd place
- European Youth Olympic Festival Netherlands, 2013 -Team Result 13th place
- World Gymnasiade Brazil, 2013 Rings 13th place

EDUCATION

Alek Manukyan 11, Yerevan September 2014 - June 2021

Alek Manukyan 1, Yerevan September 2014 - June 2020

Artistic Gymnastics

Armenian State Institute of Physical Culture

Caucasian Studies

Yerevan State University

- Member of Student Scientific Society
- Participant of Republican Conference, 2017
- Awarded for delivering an oral presentation in the 4th International Scientific Conference dedicated to the 70th anniversary of Student Scientific Society of Yerevan State University, 2017
- Awarded for delivering best speech at the 4th International Scientific Conference dedicated to the 70th anniversary of Student Scientific Society of Yerevan State University, 2017

5 Belyakov street, Yerevan July 2017 - October 2017

123 Hovsep Emin, Yerevan July 2020 - October 2020

Basics of Analytical Work

The Armenian Interest

The Basics of Programming

Russian-Armenian University

ACHIEVEMENTS

Guinness World Record, 2011 Candidate of Master of Sport of Armenia

Champion of Armenia

CERTIFICATIONS & COURSES

Certified for successful completion of the course "Basics of Analytical work: introductory course"

Certified for successful completion of course "Basics of Programming"